<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Theorems and Proofs on RSA Analysis</title>
    <link>https://prisha247.github.io/QuantumCryptography/proofs/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Theorems and Proofs on RSA Analysis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://prisha247.github.io/QuantumCryptography/proofs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Chinese Remainder Theorem</title>
      <link>https://prisha247.github.io/QuantumCryptography/proofs/crt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prisha247.github.io/QuantumCryptography/proofs/crt/</guid>
      <description>The Chinese Remainder Theorem (CRT) can help solve systems of equations for modular arithmetic equations. For example, we will use CRT to solve the below problem:
$$ x \equiv 2\ (\bmod 3)$$ $$ x \equiv 1\ (\bmod 4)$$ $$ x \equiv 3\ (\bmod 5)$$
With CRT, we can solve this system of equations as if they were three independent equations. Consider the solution for x to be in the following form:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Euler Totient Theorem</title>
      <link>https://prisha247.github.io/QuantumCryptography/proofs/post2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prisha247.github.io/QuantumCryptography/proofs/post2/</guid>
      <description>Euler’s Totient Function (mentioned as the phi function in the RSA Algorithm page) measures the &amp;ldquo;breakability of a number&amp;rdquo;. The phi function serves to calculate the number of coprimes of the product of two prime numbers, and is therefore used in the RSA algorithm to generate encryption keys (e). The greater the phi number, the more possibilities of unique encryption keys.
Suppose p and q are prime numbers. The phi function will provide the number of values which are prime relative to the product of p and q by taking the product of (p-1) and (q-1).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Fermat Little Theorem</title>
      <link>https://prisha247.github.io/QuantumCryptography/proofs/fermat-little/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://prisha247.github.io/QuantumCryptography/proofs/fermat-little/</guid>
      <description>Description Fermat&amp;rsquo;s Little Theorem, also known as Euler&amp;rsquo;s Little Theorem, is an equation that involves modular equations with exponentiation, similar to the exponentiation done in RSA. More specifically, the theorem is as follows:
$$a^p \equiv a\ (\bmod p)$$
More specifically, $a$ can be any integer, and $p$ can be any prime number.
Corollary Dividing both sides by $a$ produces this corollary. Both this form and the above form can come in handy when solving modular arithmetic equations.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
